<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>neel &#8211; IPHONE</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/neel/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>TODAY IS IPHONE DAY</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 13:26:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ID-150x150.png</url>
	<title>neel &#8211; IPHONE</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>which iphone 14 pro color is best</title>
		<link>/which-iphone-14-pro-color-is-best/</link>
					<comments>/which-iphone-14-pro-color-is-best/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 17:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[IPHONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro color]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2069</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Deep Purple is best color for iphone 14 pro If you are buying an iPhone 14 Pro or an iPhone 14 Pro Max, you have]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1><strong>Deep Purple</strong> is best color for iphone 14 pro</h1>



<p>If you are buying an iPhone 14 Pro or an iPhone 14 Pro Max, you have a choice of four different colors, which are distinct from what is available on the iPhone 14 itself. Whether you choose a standard iPhone 14 Pro or a Pro Max, the Apple iPhone 14 Pro is available in one colour, the new Deep Purple, Gold, Silver, and Space Black. There is also a new 48-megapixel main camera, an enormous bump in pixels which may well make the 14 Pro the best iPhone to take pictures with in 2022 &#8212; and the handset is available in the new, subtle colour Deep Purple.</p>



<p>In comparison, the iPhone 14 Pro and Pro Max models receive a far darker hue, which Apple calls the Deep Purple. Space Black, Silver, and Gold are all long-standing classics in iPhone color history, whereas Deep Purple (and purple, generally) is the newest hue that Apple is including in Apples iPhone line. We have seen another version of Deep Purple trim in past iPhones, but the new iPhone looks slightly different thanks to its matte back.</p>



<p>The new shade of Deep Purple was one of the most requested colors in the iPhone 14 lineup, with Apple picking it up again in 2022. Apple has been playing around with shades of their signature Red in recent years, and now we have a brighter, lighter Red color that stands out more, though some people would still revert to the Red of the iPhone 8s for a better hue &#8212; including me. The gold iPhone 14 Pro trim looks identical to previous Gold versions, but Matthew Panzarino at TechCrunch says that the Silver color looks noticeably better.</p>



<p>Here are some pictures of white/silver, and also of what the Space Black looks like when compared with the graphite color on the iPhone 13 Pro, courtesy of Panzarino. Some interesting colourways, though, do not appear the same as what you will receive with the new iPhone, so make sure you check those out too before making your purchasing decision. Silver is a color that needs little introduction &#8212; silver is one Apple has offered in the past &#8212; including in the iPhone 13 Pro lineup &#8212; and it is one other handset makers also frequently sell their devices in.</p>



<p>The shade below, Space Black &#8211; despite its name &#8211; is more a very dark gray than black, falling between the graphite shades that Apple sells phones in at times, and the midnight shades that you might be getting an iPhone 13. The iPhone 14 and the iPhone 14 Pro families come with varying colour options, so if you are firmly set on a specific hue, you might not get the model you prefer in that colour.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/which-iphone-14-pro-color-is-best/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>does iphone 14 need a screen protector</title>
		<link>/does-iphone-14-need-a-screen-protector/</link>
					<comments>/does-iphone-14-need-a-screen-protector/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 17:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[IPHONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[screen protector]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2068</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you are using the iPhone 14 Pro Max with the case on, then you do not need to worry, because that protector leaves some]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are using the iPhone 14 Pro Max with the case on, then you do not need to worry, because that protector leaves some millimeters of gap around the edges. However, you can keep the iPhone 14 Pro Maxs display free of fingerprints and reflections by using a matte glass screen protector. Even if the screen of the iPhone 14 is reinforced with ceramic shield, it may still get affected and scratched from sand.</p>



<p>Ultimately, the iPhone 14s display screen is still made from glass, and that can still get scratched by solid objects. The ceramic shield is made from material that is much harder to scratch than most metals. Ceramic Shield is unique to Apple smartphones, first introduced in the iPhone 12, promising more durable glass that will protect from knocks and falls.</p>



<p>According to Apple, Ceramic Shield in the iPhone 14 Series The iPhone 14 Series is stronger than any other smartphone glass on the market, protecting the device against spills and daily accidents. The iPhone 14 Pro uses a special kind of protective glass that Apple calls Ceramic Shield, which it says offers scratch resistance and a four-times increase in drop protection over non-Apple special glass iPhone models. This Spigen protector is rated at 9H hardness, its transparent material retains Apples iPhone 14 Pros original screen brightness and clarity, and to add insult to injury, it is also fingerprint resistant thanks to an Oleophobic coating.</p>



<p>This Spigen protector is one of the best screen protectors for this phone, as in addition to being 5X stronger, it filters out blue light for eyes protection, and is simple to install. Cornings Gorilla Glass is good at things like dropping, and keeping your iPhone from getting scuffed up from keys in the pocket, but it can still get bypassed with too much force, and scratches caused by things like sand and gravel, so a screen protector really makes sense here. If you really get a case for the iPhone 14, be sure that it is slim and lightweight; easily put on and take off; has an raised lip around the iPhone 14s glass screen (to prevent it directly touching surfaces); and has good grip, so that you can grab hold of your new iPhone 14 without dropping it.</p>



<p>You could go with a clear case on the phone, so that you can still admire the new iPhone that you bought, along with a glass tempered screen protector that will keep the screen safe from scratches and scratches, and a warranty that covers a 1-time free screen replacement (the screen is from the original manufacturer) all in one. Looking directly at the screen, you still get to enjoy a gorgeous display with bright colors, excellent clarity, and complete Face-ID functionality thanks to high-quality glass and a privacy filter.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/does-iphone-14-need-a-screen-protector/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>how to activate siri on iphone 14</title>
		<link>/how-to-activate-siri-on-iphone-14/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-activate-siri-on-iphone-14/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 17:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[IPHONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[siri on iphone 14]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2067</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Activate Siri with a button When you activate Siri with a button, Siri responds silently when iPhone is in&#160;silent mode. When silent mode is off,]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>Activate Siri with a button</h1>



<p>When you activate Siri with a button, Siri responds silently when iPhone is in&nbsp;silent mode. When silent mode is off, Siri responds out loud. To change this, see&nbsp;Change how Siri responds.</p>



<ol class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-background">
<li>Do one of the following:
<ul>
<li><em>On an iPhone with Face&nbsp;ID:</em>&nbsp;Press and hold the side button.</li>



<li><em>On an iPhone with a Home button:</em>&nbsp;Press and hold the Home button.</li>



<li><em>EarPods:</em>&nbsp;Press and hold the center or call button.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>



<p>Siri is a built-in, default personal assistant in all Apple devices, such as the iPhone, iPad, etc. It is capable of asking questions and directions, giving commands for actions to take place on a device, such as turning Bluetooth off, and more. For instance, Alexa, OK Google, Bixby, and so on Siri is the default virtual assistant on Apple devices, whether iPhone 14, iPad 12, and so on If you are really using iOS devices, then find out how to setup and use Siri on the iPhone 14. Siri first appeared on iPhone 4S, but Siri is also available on iPad, iPod touch, Apple Watch, AirPods, HomePod, and the Mac (macOS Sierra and higher) &#8212; see our guide on Siri on macOS.</p>



<p>This article covers how to enable and access Siri on iPhone 12, what you can do with Siri, and how to use an Intercom-like mode. We hope that this article on iPhone 14 helps you out and solves all of your problems. Once you have enabled Siri in your iPhone 12, all you have to do is either say Hey Siri or long-press on the right-hand side button to get to Siri.</p>



<p>If you have enabled Hey Siri, you can just say Hey Siri aloud next to your iPhone 14 to activate it. If you would like to use Hey Siri when the iPhone is face-down or covered, head into Settings &gt; Accessibility &gt; Siri and turn on Always Listen For Hey Siri option.</p>



<p>If you select the second option while turning on your Virtual Assistant on your iPhone 14, which is the side-button pressed option for Siri, you can hold the power button and Siri will begin talking to you. Another way of activating Siri on the iPhone 13 smartphone is by pressing and holding the side button on your iPhone 13, then Siri will open.</p>



<p>On the iPhone or iPad, Siri can be activated either by holding down the Home key on compatible models, or holding down the Side button on devices that do not have a home key. Most Apple devices support the command to trigger Siri with the command Hey, Siri, but newer iPads, iPhones, Macs, and Apple Watches provide hands-free Siri support with the command Hey, Siri, even when disconnected from power.</p>



<p>The minute you unplug your iPhone 6 or older, you cannot use just your voice to activate Hey Siri. In addition to the neat feature of Hey Siri, which lets you call Siri simply by calling out to it, even when the device is asleep, you can still physically activate Siri on Face ID models by holding down the large side button for two to three seconds. Now, to turn Siri suggestions on or off from either the lock screen or within apps, head into the Siri and search screen, scroll down and choose your desired app, and select the desired toggle to toggle Siri suggestions on or off.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-activate-siri-on-iphone-14/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>what does sos mean on iphone 14</title>
		<link>/what-does-sos-mean-on-iphone-14/</link>
					<comments>/what-does-sos-mean-on-iphone-14/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 17:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[IPHONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sos mean on iphone 14]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2066</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Months after its announcement at Septembers event, Apples satellite-based emergency notification service, which uses satellites to route emergency calls to the iPhone 14 and iPhone]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Months after its announcement at Septembers event, Apples satellite-based emergency notification service, which uses satellites to route emergency calls to the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Pro, launched today. By adding SOS via satellite to its latest iPhones, Apple is taking what was a niche security feature and offering it to millions of iPhone 14 owners. Apple is rolling out a new feature that allows its latest iPhones to communicate with low-Earth orbiting satellites and transmit information back to the teams of emergency responders.</p>



<p>Apple built a new interface that lets users send messages to emergency services via satellite using a questionnaire that asks key questions to help first responders understand an emergency situation and dispatch assistance. Apple has built a new interface that allows users to send messages to emergency services over satellite using a questionnaire that asks critical questions for first responders to understand the emergency and dispatch help. Well, just like its name suggests, this feature allows you to tap into satellite and send a distress message to either emergency services providers or an Apple Relay Center, who will be able to call on your behalf to get assistance. Apple launched its emergency service through satellite feature back on November 15, 2022. At the time of its release, the emergency service through satellite feature was available only in the United States and Canada, but since December 14, France, Germany, Ireland, and the United Kingdom. At this point, Apples Emergency Service Through Satellite feature is available only in the United States, and as of December 14, France, Germany, Ireland, and the United Kingdom. At this point, Apples emergency through satellite function is only available in the United States, and Canada. Well, let us find out.Well, just as the name implies, when you do not have reception, the feature lets you connect to a satellite and send an SOS message to an emergency services provider or an Apple relay center, which can call for assistance on your behalf.Apple launched the Emergency SOS via satellite feature on November 15th, 2022.At launch, the Emergency SOS via satellite feature was only available in the US and Canada, but as of December 14th, it is also available in France, Germany, Ireland, and the UK.Currently, only the latest iPhone 14 lineup supports Apples Emergency SOS via satellite feature. As noted above, it is unfortunately missing those purchased on the Chinese mainland, in Hong Kong, or in Macao.</p>



<p>Typically, if the phone does not have the service, it gives you a heads-up that you can still use it to dial 911, either showing text such as Emergency Call Only, or, in the case of iOS 16, a badge. It turns out SOS on the status bar is the way that Apple is now signaling that a phone is not connected to the cell network, but it is still capable of making 911 calls. If your iPhone is not properly connected to a cellular network, you will be able to find SOS, or simply an SOS, at the upper-right corner on iOS 16, or at the upper-left corner on iOS 15 and below.</p>



<p>In short, an SOS icon means the iPhone is out of range of your carrier, but does not disable 911 calls. The SOS icon, or text with only the letters SOS, that typically appears on the upper-right of the iPhone in iOS 16, or upper-left in earlier versions, indicates there is an issue with the cell networks. You are guided through to the satellite-connection stage after answering emergency questions and are ready to send your compressed, encrypted, message.</p>



<p>You are then guided into holding your iPhone 14 down in order to make the connection with a visible satellite above your head, and to get the message through to the emergency response team. You get the same hand-held satellite-positioning bits that are in the emergency part, and Apple will then show you the message has been sent.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/what-does-sos-mean-on-iphone-14/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>how to factory reset iphone</title>
		<link>/how-to-factory-reset-iphone/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-factory-reset-iphone/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 17:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[IPHONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[factory reset]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2065</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Use Settings to erase iPhone Factory Resets erase all your personal information, returning your iPhone to the original factory settings. Once you have completed the]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>Use Settings to erase iPhone</h1>



<ol class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-background">
<li>Go to Settings&nbsp;<img decoding="async" src="https://help.apple.com/assets/634D93C867B48F12442A1784/634D93C967B48F12442A1792/en_US/88b2400e45bcf521514b7252cbb2d959.png" alt="" height="30" width="30">&nbsp;&gt; General&nbsp;&gt; Transfer or Reset iPhone.</li>



<li>Do one of the following:
<ul>
<li><em>Prepare your content and settings to transfer to a new iPhone:&nbsp;</em>Tap Get Started, then follow the onscreen instructions. When you finish, return to Settings&nbsp;&gt; General&nbsp;&gt; Transfer or Reset iPhone, then tap Erase All Content and Settings.</li>



<li><em>Erase all of your data from iPhone:&nbsp;</em>Tap Erase All Content and Settings.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>



<p>Factory Resets erase all your personal information, returning your iPhone to the original factory settings. Once you have completed the restore process&#8211;a process that can take up to several minutes&#8211;check to make sure that your phone has been restored to its original factory settings. If you wish to reset the iPhone back to the factory state, click on the &#8220;Erase All Content and Settings&#8221; option.</p>



<p>Another route you can take for resetting your iPhone is through the Settings menu on the phone itself, provided that you can navigate beyond the Home screen. If you are experiencing issues on an iPhone, such as your iPhone freezing or malfunctioning, then returning your device to the factory settings can fix the problem. You can perform the restore straight from your iPhone, without the need for iTunes, but this process is not available if your phone is turned off or stuck in recovery mode.</p>



<p>Yes, you can place your iPhone into DFU mode, attach it to iTunes, choose &#8220;Restore,&#8221; and your phone is fully restored. Once you have completed the restore, now you can unplug your iPhone from your computer, then setup and use the iPhone like it is brand new. In case, you enabled Find my iPhone, you can also use iCloud to restore the factory settings of the iPhone, even when you forget your devices password.</p>



<p>You will have to enter in your Apple ID password to confirm the Reset, and your iPhone will wipe all content from the storage, returning you to the original configuration screen that you saw when you first used your device. Once you have entered either the passcode or your Apple ID, the iPhone will start wiping out its data, apps, and settings. Or any other major issue How to Use Hold down the Power Button and Turn Off Your Device Hold down both power button and volume buttons together for 20 seconds until you see the Apple logo. Select the Erase option from iPhone Settings, or Restore Your Phone What happens is just reboot the iPhone.</p>



<p>Do not let go of the right button until you see a recovery mode screen appear (you may see the icon of the Computer and a USB cable) on the iPhone. If you really want to turn off your iPhone 14, you can do that by going into the General section of the Settings app, scrolling to the bottom, and selecting the Power Off option. A total wipe is something of a nuclear option, however, so before going this route, you would want to consider rebooting or forcing your iPhone or iPad into recovery mode, since those will keep your data and settings intact.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-factory-reset-iphone/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>how to screen record on iphone</title>
		<link>/how-to-screen-record-on-iphone/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-screen-record-on-iphone/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 17:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[IPHONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[screen record]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2064</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[How to record your screen Go to&#160;the Photos app&#160;and select your screen recording. The Screen Recording function on iPhones and iPads Your iPhones and iPads]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>How to record your screen</h1>



<ol class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-background">
<li>Go to Settings &gt; Control Center, then tap the Add button&nbsp;<img decoding="async" alt="" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/ios13-add-icon.png" width="22">&nbsp;next to Screen Recording.</li>



<li>Open Control Center on your iPhone,&nbsp;or on your&nbsp;iPad.</li>



<li>Tap the gray Record button&nbsp;<img decoding="async" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/ios14-record-icon.png" alt="gray record icon" width="20">,&nbsp;then wait for the three-second countown.</li>



<li>Exit Control Center to record your screen.</li>



<li>To stop recording, open Control Center,&nbsp;then tap the red Record button&nbsp;<img decoding="async" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/ios11-control-center-screen-record-icon.png" alt="red record icon" width="20">. Or tap the red status bar at the top of your screen and tap Stop.</li>
</ol>



<p>Go to&nbsp;the Photos app&nbsp;and select your screen recording.</p>



<p>The Screen Recording function on iPhones and iPads Your iPhones and iPads may have this handy feature, and this tutorial shows how to configure screen recording function on your iPhones and iPads. The first thing you will want to do is enable the screen recording feature on your device, you can do that in the Settings menu of your iPhone or iPad. If you are using an iPhone or iPad and are wondering how to record the screen, the process may not be that obvious.</p>



<p>There is one relatively simple method for recording your face and screen simultaneously, if that is something that interests you. If you would prefer to take a video record of the Apple iPhones screen rather than a static screenshot, that is also something you can do. If you would like to take video of the screen of an iPhone or iPad, you do not have to even download an app to accomplish this task.</p>



<p>If you are an iPhone, iPad, or iPod Touch owner, there is no longer any need to use a ton of apps to capture the screens on your devices. This makes it a lot easier than going through third-party apps to record the activities on your iPhone or iPads screen. Now that you know this neat hack to capture the screen on an iPhone, it is also something that can be used on an Apple iPad device.</p>



<p>This is really useful functionality if you are looking to record a quick video on how to do something on an iPhone or iPad, or you are looking to record your gaming skills, etc. You might want to do more with your recordings than is typically available on an iPhone. Fortunately, there are other screen recorder apps that work with the iPhone that offer far more advanced features, such as the iPhone screen recording app Screencast-o-matic, which lets you record your screen, add comments, edit your recordings, and easily share the recordings.</p>



<p>Adding subtitling and captions to your iPhone screen recordings using the free app means that you can be sure you are hitting the mark accessibility-wise. The iPhones native screen recording tools come with limited features, one being that while you can screen record and include subtitling or captioning, you cannot edit it. Along with all of the features and benefits discussed above, the free application is continually updated in order to deliver an improved product to users who use the service, as well as more features.</p>



<p>Screencast-O-Matics screen recording app for iPhone makes screen recording incredibly simple, so you can make &#8220;how-to&#8221; videos, product demonstrations, or even just fun moments to share with friends. With the iPhones screen recorder features, you can keep favorite YouTube clips, make tutorials for your friends, or even record gameplay sequences in a few taps. Once you have downloaded Record It!, take the following steps to make sure that your Recorder is readily available from the Control panel of your iPhone.</p>



<p>If the Recording function is not already under a section called &#8220;Included controls,&#8221; swipe down to &#8220;More controls&#8221; and tap the green plus sign next to it. To access Record, swipe down from the upper right side of your screen, which brings up your Control Center. If you have an iPhone X or higher, swipe from the top right corner down to access the Control Center, and tap on the gray Record button on the bottom of the screen.</p>



<p>If you have the iPhone 8, SE, or older, swipe upwards from the bottom of the screen, and then tap on the Record. If you do not want a screen recording button in Control Center anymore, you can easily remove the screen recording button by returning to Controls, then tapping on the red &#8212; sign. If you wish to turn off the sound, just hold the record button again and tap the mic symbol again to turn it off.</p>



<p>If you do not want to use the microphone, you can turn it off by returning to the pop-up and clicking the microphone icon. The grey record button will also record your voice if you enable the mic feature (to access it, press and hold the Record button to bring up a pop-up menu). To begin using recording, just tap on the record icon, which starts a three-second countdown timer to get you into what you want to record.</p>



<p>To begin, navigate to an app or website that you would like to record, so that when recording starts, there are less steps you need to perform. You will know that you are still recording because the time shown on the top-left corner will be red. A countdown timer of three seconds will show up, then the clock at the top left corner of your screen will be turned red.</p>



<p>While the phone is recording, the screen will display a red record icon, or alert, at the upper right. Once recording has started, you will see a red symbol appear in the upper-right corner, which indicates your iPhones screen is being recorded. Once the recording is complete, the alert will inform you that a video has been recorded and stored in the devices Photo Album.</p>



<p>By default, recordings are saved in your Photos album, but you can select another destination from a list provided when you press the Record button for longer. If you wish to record both the screen and audio, long-press the Screen Recording icon, click on the microphone audio icon to enable, tap Start recording, wait 3 seconds, and your screen recording will start. Taking a screenshot &#8212; a single, static picture of the screen of your device, whether that is your iPhone, a Mac or your Apple Watch &#8212; is easy enough.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-screen-record-on-iphone/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>how to pair airpods with a non-Apple device</title>
		<link>/how-to-pair-airpods-with-a-non-apple-device/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-pair-airpods-with-a-non-apple-device/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 17:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AIRPODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pair airpods with a non-Apple device]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2062</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Use AirPods with a non-Apple device You can use&#160;AirPods as a Bluetooth headset with a non-Apple device. You can&#8217;t use Siri, but you can listen]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>Use AirPods with a non-Apple device</h1>



<p>You can use&nbsp;AirPods as a Bluetooth headset with a non-Apple device. You can&#8217;t use Siri, but you can listen and talk. To set up your AirPods&nbsp;with an Android phone or other non-Apple device,<sup>3</sup>&nbsp;follow these steps:</p>



<ol class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-background">
<li>On your non-Apple device, go to the settings for Bluetooth and make sure that Bluetooth is on.<sup>4</sup>&nbsp;If you have an Android device, go to Settings &gt; Connections &gt; Bluetooth.</li>



<li>With your&nbsp;AirPods in the charging case, open the lid.</li>



<li>Press and hold the setup button on the back of the case until the status light flashes white.</li>



<li>When your&nbsp;AirPods appear in the list of Bluetooth devices, select them.</li>
</ol>



<p>If you paired AirPods Pro with an iPhone, and you want to now switch to a different phone, you will need to press the pairing button on the charging cover and follow the on-screen instructions. With the cases still open, position AirPods or AirPods Pro next to an iPhone or iPad, and follow the instructions on-screen to pair. For the AirPods and AirPods Pro, open the case, hold them next to an Android device, tap the white button on the back until a list of connected devices appears on your screen, then tap Connect.</p>



<p>If Apples AirPods Pro is connected to an Android phone, enable Bluetooth on an iPhone/iPad, and find the device, then tap on the AirPods Pro to connect to an iOS device. If Apples AirPods are not automatically connected to your Android device, you can go to the apps settings and turn on the &#8220;Autoconnect&#8221; option. Now, you can open the Bluetooth menu on another device, look for the listing for the AirPods Pro, and connect the AirPods Pro.</p>



<p>Your AirPods should then appear in the &#8220;Add device&#8221; window of the PCs Bluetooth settings, where you can tap pairing and connecting. The next time you want to connect, search your AirPods on your list of Bluetooth devices that are available, and tap Connect if it does not automatically.</p>



<p>Look for your AirPods in your Bluetooth settings and check that they are connected: If they are not, open your AirPods casing and select your AirPods from the Bluetooth section to connect. If you have several Bluetooth headphones, speakers, and other audio devices, your iPhone may want to connect automatically with several Bluetooth headphones before the AirPods. You are not limited to Apple-made gadgets; thanks to the power of Bluetooth, the AirPods can connect with Android devices, as well as your PC.</p>



<p>Thanks to the dedicated chip inside its charging case, connecting the AirPods with an iPhone or iPad is a breeze: just pop open the case next to your AirPods, then tap Connect. Simply press and hold the rear button of the charging case while it is open with the AirPods inside to start the pairing process. To pair AirPods, turn on Bluetooth on an iOS device by opening Control Center, and then tapping the Bluetooth icon to turn on Bluetooth.</p>



<p>After making an initial connection between the Windows 10 PC and Apple AirPods, you can re-connect your AirPods and the Windows 10 PC for listening to music, watching YouTube, video conferencing, and more by going back to the Bluetooth and Other Devices page under Settings. If audio does not immediately sound like it should, you might have to click either the Volume Control or Bluetooth menus on your menu bar, and ensure Apple AirPods has been set up as an output device.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-pair-airpods-with-a-non-apple-device/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>how to reset airpods</title>
		<link>/how-to-reset-airpods/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-reset-airpods/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 17:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AIRPODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reset airpods]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You may need to reset your AirPods if they won&#8217;t charge, or to fix a different issue.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>You may need to reset your AirPods if they won&#8217;t charge, or to fix a different issue.</h1>



<ol class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-background">
<li>Put your AirPods in their charging case and close the lid.</li>



<li>Wait 30 seconds.</li>



<li>Open the lid of your charging case, and put your AirPods in your ears.</li>



<li>Go to Settings&nbsp;&gt; Bluetooth. Or go to&nbsp;Settings &gt; [your AirPods].
<ul>
<li>If your AirPods appear there as connected, tap the More Info button&nbsp;<img decoding="async" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/ios14-info-icon.png" alt="" width="22">&nbsp;next to your AirPods, tap Forget This Device, then tap again to confirm.</li>



<li>If your AirPods don&#8217;t appear there, continue to the next step.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li>Put your AirPods in their charging case, and keep the lid open.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Press and hold the setup button on the back of the case for about 15 seconds, until the status light on the front of the case&nbsp;flashes amber, then white.</li>



<li>Reconnect your AirPods: With your AirPods in their charging case and&nbsp;the lid open, place your AirPods close to your&nbsp;iPhone&nbsp;or iPad. Follow the steps on your device&#8217;s screen.</li>



<li>AirPods can be associated with one Apple ID. If you want to use AirPods (3rd generation) or AirPods Pro (1st or 2nd generation) that someone else has used, they&#8217;ll first need to&nbsp;remove the AirPods from their Apple ID.</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-reset-airpods/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>how to connect airpods to mac</title>
		<link>/how-to-connect-airpods-to-mac/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-connect-airpods-to-mac/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 17:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AIRPODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[connect airpods to mac]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2061</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you&#8217;ve set up your AirPods with your iPhone and your Mac is signed in to iCloud with the same Apple ID, your AirPods&#160;may be]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you&#8217;ve set up your AirPods with your iPhone and your Mac is signed in to iCloud with the same Apple ID, your AirPods&nbsp;may be ready to use with your Mac. Place your AirPods in your ears and click either the Bluetooth menu&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-bluetooth-icon.png" alt="" width="25" height="38"/></figure>



<p>&nbsp;or the volume control&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/airpods/macos-airpods-pro-volume-control-status-bar-icon.png" alt="" width="46" height="30"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-big-sur-volume-status-icon.png" alt="" width="48" height="37"/></figure>



<p>&nbsp;in the menu bar on your Mac.<sup>1</sup>&nbsp;Then choose your AirPods from the list.</p>



<h2>If your AirPods haven&#8217;t appeared&nbsp;in the Bluetooth&nbsp;<img decoding="async" width="13" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-bluetooth-icon.png" alt="">&nbsp;or volume control&nbsp;<img decoding="async" width="22" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-big-sur-volume-status-icon.png" alt="">&nbsp;menu,&nbsp;pair your AirPods with your Mac:</h2>



<ol class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-background">
<li>On your Mac, choose System&nbsp;Settings&nbsp;from the Apple menu , then click Bluetooth.</li>



<li>Make sure Bluetooth is turned on.</li>



<li>Put both AirPods in the charging case&nbsp;and open the lid.</li>



<li>Press and hold the setup button on the back of the case until the status light starts flashing white.</li>



<li>Select your AirPods in the Devices list, then click Connect.</li>
</ol>



<p>If sound is still playing from your Mac speakers, click either the Bluetooth menu&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-bluetooth-icon.png" alt="" width="28" height="42"/></figure>



<p>&nbsp;or the volume control&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-big-sur-volume-status-icon.png" alt="" width="37" height="29"/></figure>



<p>&nbsp;in the menu bar and make sure your&nbsp;AirPods are selected as the output device.</p>



<p></p>



<p>ou can go into your Apps folder using Finder, choose System Preferences, click Bluetooth, right-click on the AirPods from within your Devices window, and choose Connect to pair the AirPods with your Mac. Place your AirPods in pairing mode by opening their charging case and placing them next to the Mac.</p>



<p>If you do not have your iPhone handy, you can place them back into the charging case with the cover opened. If your AirPods are already connected to an iPhone, you should be able to select the AirPods from the volume icons on the menu bar. If your AirPods or AirPods Pro are paired, but are not connected, you can tap on the Volume Control button in the menu bar, and choose your headphones to switch between them.</p>



<p>If you chose to add Bluetooth to the menu bar, you can tap that icon at any time to check your AirPods battery life and toggle modes with AirPods Pro. To check, put Apples AirPods (2017) into your ears, then look at the drop-down menu for either Bluetooth or Volume in your Macs menu bar. If you are still hearing audio coming through their MacBooks speakers, choose either the Bluetooth or volume controls in the menu bar, and make sure that either the AirPods or the AirPods Pro are selected as your output device.</p>



<p>If your AirPods are connected to the same Apple ID as your MacBook, and are set up via your iPhone already, open the cover on the enclosure closest to the MacBook. Your AirPods are designed to connect to your Mac automatically as long as your Mac uses the same Apple ID as your iPhone. Using AirBuddy ($5.00), you can view your AirPods or AirPods Pros connectivity status by opening the devices charging case next to your Mac.</p>



<p>In the event that you paired the AirPods Pro to an iPhone, and you want to now switch to a different phone, you will need to hold down the pairing button on the charging case and follow the on-screen instructions. If you would prefer to keep the pairing process closer to how you would do on iPhone or iPad &#8212; usually, you will not need to press a button, either &#8212; then you can use a third-party app to achieve a similar iPhone-like experience for AirPods or AirPods Pro on a Mac. If your AirPods are not doing this (if, say, they are pairing with an iPhone instead), just tap the Bluetooth icon on the Macs menu bar, choose your AirPods from the drop-down list, and click Connect.</p>



<p>If you paired your AirPods to an iPhone, and your Mac is signed into the same iCloud account as your iPhone, place your AirPods in your ears and open the Bluetooth app on your Mac, clicking the Bluetooth icon in the menu bar, clicking on the name you gave your AirPods, and choosing Connect</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-connect-airpods-to-mac/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>are airpods waterproof : get the information</title>
		<link>/are-airpods-waterproof-get-the-information/</link>
					<comments>/are-airpods-waterproof-get-the-information/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 17:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AIRPODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[airpods waterproof]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[the answers is yes and also no ,it depends on which type of airpods it is. AirPods (2nd generation) is not waterproof but AirPods (3rd]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>the answers is yes and also no ,it depends on which type of airpods it is.</p>



<p>AirPods (2nd generation) is not waterproof but AirPods (3rd generation) and AirPods&nbsp;Pro (2nd generation) is waterproof</p>



<p></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/are-airpods-waterproof-get-the-information/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
