<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>AIRPODS &#8211; IPHONE</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/airpods/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>TODAY IS IPHONE DAY</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 13:26:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ID-150x150.png</url>
	<title>AIRPODS &#8211; IPHONE</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>how to pair airpods with a non-Apple device</title>
		<link>/how-to-pair-airpods-with-a-non-apple-device/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-pair-airpods-with-a-non-apple-device/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 17:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AIRPODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pair airpods with a non-Apple device]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2062</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Use AirPods with a non-Apple device You can use&#160;AirPods as a Bluetooth headset with a non-Apple device. You can&#8217;t use Siri, but you can listen]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>Use AirPods with a non-Apple device</h1>



<p>You can use&nbsp;AirPods as a Bluetooth headset with a non-Apple device. You can&#8217;t use Siri, but you can listen and talk. To set up your AirPods&nbsp;with an Android phone or other non-Apple device,<sup>3</sup>&nbsp;follow these steps:</p>



<ol class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-background">
<li>On your non-Apple device, go to the settings for Bluetooth and make sure that Bluetooth is on.<sup>4</sup>&nbsp;If you have an Android device, go to Settings &gt; Connections &gt; Bluetooth.</li>



<li>With your&nbsp;AirPods in the charging case, open the lid.</li>



<li>Press and hold the setup button on the back of the case until the status light flashes white.</li>



<li>When your&nbsp;AirPods appear in the list of Bluetooth devices, select them.</li>
</ol>



<p>If you paired AirPods Pro with an iPhone, and you want to now switch to a different phone, you will need to press the pairing button on the charging cover and follow the on-screen instructions. With the cases still open, position AirPods or AirPods Pro next to an iPhone or iPad, and follow the instructions on-screen to pair. For the AirPods and AirPods Pro, open the case, hold them next to an Android device, tap the white button on the back until a list of connected devices appears on your screen, then tap Connect.</p>



<p>If Apples AirPods Pro is connected to an Android phone, enable Bluetooth on an iPhone/iPad, and find the device, then tap on the AirPods Pro to connect to an iOS device. If Apples AirPods are not automatically connected to your Android device, you can go to the apps settings and turn on the &#8220;Autoconnect&#8221; option. Now, you can open the Bluetooth menu on another device, look for the listing for the AirPods Pro, and connect the AirPods Pro.</p>



<p>Your AirPods should then appear in the &#8220;Add device&#8221; window of the PCs Bluetooth settings, where you can tap pairing and connecting. The next time you want to connect, search your AirPods on your list of Bluetooth devices that are available, and tap Connect if it does not automatically.</p>



<p>Look for your AirPods in your Bluetooth settings and check that they are connected: If they are not, open your AirPods casing and select your AirPods from the Bluetooth section to connect. If you have several Bluetooth headphones, speakers, and other audio devices, your iPhone may want to connect automatically with several Bluetooth headphones before the AirPods. You are not limited to Apple-made gadgets; thanks to the power of Bluetooth, the AirPods can connect with Android devices, as well as your PC.</p>



<p>Thanks to the dedicated chip inside its charging case, connecting the AirPods with an iPhone or iPad is a breeze: just pop open the case next to your AirPods, then tap Connect. Simply press and hold the rear button of the charging case while it is open with the AirPods inside to start the pairing process. To pair AirPods, turn on Bluetooth on an iOS device by opening Control Center, and then tapping the Bluetooth icon to turn on Bluetooth.</p>



<p>After making an initial connection between the Windows 10 PC and Apple AirPods, you can re-connect your AirPods and the Windows 10 PC for listening to music, watching YouTube, video conferencing, and more by going back to the Bluetooth and Other Devices page under Settings. If audio does not immediately sound like it should, you might have to click either the Volume Control or Bluetooth menus on your menu bar, and ensure Apple AirPods has been set up as an output device.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-pair-airpods-with-a-non-apple-device/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>how to reset airpods</title>
		<link>/how-to-reset-airpods/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-reset-airpods/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 17:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AIRPODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reset airpods]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You may need to reset your AirPods if they won&#8217;t charge, or to fix a different issue.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>You may need to reset your AirPods if they won&#8217;t charge, or to fix a different issue.</h1>



<ol class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-background">
<li>Put your AirPods in their charging case and close the lid.</li>



<li>Wait 30 seconds.</li>



<li>Open the lid of your charging case, and put your AirPods in your ears.</li>



<li>Go to Settings&nbsp;&gt; Bluetooth. Or go to&nbsp;Settings &gt; [your AirPods].
<ul>
<li>If your AirPods appear there as connected, tap the More Info button&nbsp;<img decoding="async" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/ios14-info-icon.png" alt="" width="22">&nbsp;next to your AirPods, tap Forget This Device, then tap again to confirm.</li>



<li>If your AirPods don&#8217;t appear there, continue to the next step.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li>Put your AirPods in their charging case, and keep the lid open.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Press and hold the setup button on the back of the case for about 15 seconds, until the status light on the front of the case&nbsp;flashes amber, then white.</li>



<li>Reconnect your AirPods: With your AirPods in their charging case and&nbsp;the lid open, place your AirPods close to your&nbsp;iPhone&nbsp;or iPad. Follow the steps on your device&#8217;s screen.</li>



<li>AirPods can be associated with one Apple ID. If you want to use AirPods (3rd generation) or AirPods Pro (1st or 2nd generation) that someone else has used, they&#8217;ll first need to&nbsp;remove the AirPods from their Apple ID.</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-reset-airpods/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>how to connect airpods to mac</title>
		<link>/how-to-connect-airpods-to-mac/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-connect-airpods-to-mac/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 17:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AIRPODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[connect airpods to mac]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2061</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you&#8217;ve set up your AirPods with your iPhone and your Mac is signed in to iCloud with the same Apple ID, your AirPods&#160;may be]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you&#8217;ve set up your AirPods with your iPhone and your Mac is signed in to iCloud with the same Apple ID, your AirPods&nbsp;may be ready to use with your Mac. Place your AirPods in your ears and click either the Bluetooth menu&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-bluetooth-icon.png" alt="" width="25" height="38"/></figure>



<p>&nbsp;or the volume control&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/airpods/macos-airpods-pro-volume-control-status-bar-icon.png" alt="" width="46" height="30"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-big-sur-volume-status-icon.png" alt="" width="48" height="37"/></figure>



<p>&nbsp;in the menu bar on your Mac.<sup>1</sup>&nbsp;Then choose your AirPods from the list.</p>



<h2>If your AirPods haven&#8217;t appeared&nbsp;in the Bluetooth&nbsp;<img decoding="async" width="13" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-bluetooth-icon.png" alt="">&nbsp;or volume control&nbsp;<img decoding="async" width="22" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-big-sur-volume-status-icon.png" alt="">&nbsp;menu,&nbsp;pair your AirPods with your Mac:</h2>



<ol class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-background">
<li>On your Mac, choose System&nbsp;Settings&nbsp;from the Apple menu , then click Bluetooth.</li>



<li>Make sure Bluetooth is turned on.</li>



<li>Put both AirPods in the charging case&nbsp;and open the lid.</li>



<li>Press and hold the setup button on the back of the case until the status light starts flashing white.</li>



<li>Select your AirPods in the Devices list, then click Connect.</li>
</ol>



<p>If sound is still playing from your Mac speakers, click either the Bluetooth menu&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-bluetooth-icon.png" alt="" width="28" height="42"/></figure>



<p>&nbsp;or the volume control&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://support.apple.com/library/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/il/macos-big-sur-volume-status-icon.png" alt="" width="37" height="29"/></figure>



<p>&nbsp;in the menu bar and make sure your&nbsp;AirPods are selected as the output device.</p>



<p></p>



<p>ou can go into your Apps folder using Finder, choose System Preferences, click Bluetooth, right-click on the AirPods from within your Devices window, and choose Connect to pair the AirPods with your Mac. Place your AirPods in pairing mode by opening their charging case and placing them next to the Mac.</p>



<p>If you do not have your iPhone handy, you can place them back into the charging case with the cover opened. If your AirPods are already connected to an iPhone, you should be able to select the AirPods from the volume icons on the menu bar. If your AirPods or AirPods Pro are paired, but are not connected, you can tap on the Volume Control button in the menu bar, and choose your headphones to switch between them.</p>



<p>If you chose to add Bluetooth to the menu bar, you can tap that icon at any time to check your AirPods battery life and toggle modes with AirPods Pro. To check, put Apples AirPods (2017) into your ears, then look at the drop-down menu for either Bluetooth or Volume in your Macs menu bar. If you are still hearing audio coming through their MacBooks speakers, choose either the Bluetooth or volume controls in the menu bar, and make sure that either the AirPods or the AirPods Pro are selected as your output device.</p>



<p>If your AirPods are connected to the same Apple ID as your MacBook, and are set up via your iPhone already, open the cover on the enclosure closest to the MacBook. Your AirPods are designed to connect to your Mac automatically as long as your Mac uses the same Apple ID as your iPhone. Using AirBuddy ($5.00), you can view your AirPods or AirPods Pros connectivity status by opening the devices charging case next to your Mac.</p>



<p>In the event that you paired the AirPods Pro to an iPhone, and you want to now switch to a different phone, you will need to hold down the pairing button on the charging case and follow the on-screen instructions. If you would prefer to keep the pairing process closer to how you would do on iPhone or iPad &#8212; usually, you will not need to press a button, either &#8212; then you can use a third-party app to achieve a similar iPhone-like experience for AirPods or AirPods Pro on a Mac. If your AirPods are not doing this (if, say, they are pairing with an iPhone instead), just tap the Bluetooth icon on the Macs menu bar, choose your AirPods from the drop-down list, and click Connect.</p>



<p>If you paired your AirPods to an iPhone, and your Mac is signed into the same iCloud account as your iPhone, place your AirPods in your ears and open the Bluetooth app on your Mac, clicking the Bluetooth icon in the menu bar, clicking on the name you gave your AirPods, and choosing Connect</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-connect-airpods-to-mac/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>are airpods waterproof : get the information</title>
		<link>/are-airpods-waterproof-get-the-information/</link>
					<comments>/are-airpods-waterproof-get-the-information/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 17:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AIRPODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[airpods waterproof]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[the answers is yes and also no ,it depends on which type of airpods it is. AirPods (2nd generation) is not waterproof but AirPods (3rd]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>the answers is yes and also no ,it depends on which type of airpods it is.</p>



<p>AirPods (2nd generation) is not waterproof but AirPods (3rd generation) and AirPods&nbsp;Pro (2nd generation) is waterproof</p>



<p></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/are-airpods-waterproof-get-the-information/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>how to connect airpods to iphone</title>
		<link>/how-to-connect-airpods-to-iphone/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-connect-airpods-to-iphone/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 17:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AIRPODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[connect airpods to iphone]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2059</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Connect your AirPods and AirPods Pro to your iPhone three simple steps to connect airpods to iphone]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Connect your AirPods and AirPods Pro to your iPhone</p>



<h2>three simple steps to connect airpods to iphone</h2>



<ol>
<li>Go to the Home Screen.</li>



<li>With your AirPods in the charging case, open the charging case and hold it next to your iPhone.&nbsp;A setup animation will appear on your iPhone.</li>



<li>Tap Connect.&nbsp;</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-connect-airpods-to-iphone/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>how much are airpods</title>
		<link>/how-much-are-airpods/</link>
					<comments>/how-much-are-airpods/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[neel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 17:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AIRPODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how much are airpods]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.iphone.day/?p=2058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[AirPods&#160;(2nd generation) Double-tap H1 chip Hey&#160;Siri Up to 5 hours of listening time on one charge More than 24 hours of listening time with charging]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="has-text-align-center has-vivid-red-color has-text-color"><br>AirPods&nbsp;(2nd generation)</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Opera-Snapshot_2022-12-16_211343_www.apple_.com_.png" alt="" class="wp-image-2083" width="188" height="217"/></figure></div>


<div class="is-layout-constrained wp-block-group has-black-color has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-text-color has-background"><div class="wp-block-group__inner-container">
<p>Double-tap</p>



<p>H1 chip</p>



<p>Hey&nbsp;Siri</p>



<p>Up to 5 hours of listening time on one charge</p>



<p>More than 24 hours of listening time with charging case</p>



<p>Automatic switching</p>



<p>Personalized engraving</p>



<p>Lightning Charging Case</p>
</div></div>



<h2 class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-text-color has-background" style="color:#174319">AirPods&nbsp;(2nd generation) price is $129</h2>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center has-vivid-red-color has-text-color">AirPods&nbsp;(3rd generation)</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Opera-Snapshot_2022-12-16_212124_www.apple_.com_.png" alt="" class="wp-image-2084" width="235" height="223"/></figure></div>


<div class="is-layout-constrained wp-block-group has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"><div class="wp-block-group__inner-container">
<p>Force sensor</p>



<p>Personalized Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking</p>



<p>Sweat and water resistant: AirPods and charging case</p>



<p>H1 chip</p>



<p>Hey&nbsp;Siri</p>



<p>Up to 6 hours of listening time on one charge</p>



<p>Up to 30 hours of listening time with charging case</p>



<p>Automatic switching</p>



<p>Personalized engraving</p>



<p>Lightning Charging Case</p>
</div></div>



<h2 class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-text-color has-background" style="color:#1c5532">AirPods&nbsp;(3rd generation) price is $169</h2>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center has-vivid-red-color has-text-color">AirPods&nbsp;Pro (2nd generation)</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Opera-Snapshot_2022-12-16_215701_www.apple_.com_.png" alt="" class="wp-image-2085" width="254" height="201"/></figure></div>


<div class="is-layout-constrained wp-block-group has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"><div class="wp-block-group__inner-container">
<p>Active Noise Cancellation</p>



<p>Adaptive Transparency</p>



<p>Touch control</p>



<p>Personalized Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking</p>



<p>Sweat and water resistant: AirPods&nbsp;Pro and charging case</p>



<p>H2 chip</p>



<p>Hey&nbsp;Siri</p>



<p>Up to 6 hours of listening time on one charge</p>



<p>Up to 30 hours of listening time with charging case</p>



<p>Automatic switching</p>



<p>Personalized engraving</p>



<p>MagSafe Charging Case with speaker and lanyard&nbsp;loop</p>
</div></div>



<h2 class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-text-color has-background" style="color:#15471d">AirPods&nbsp;Pro (2nd generation) price is $249</h2>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center has-vivid-red-color has-text-color">AirPods&nbsp;Max</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Opera-Snapshot_2022-12-16_215747_www.apple_.com_.png" alt="" class="wp-image-2086" width="237" height="230"/></figure></div>


<div class="is-layout-constrained wp-block-group has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"><div class="wp-block-group__inner-container">
<p>Active Noise Cancellation<br>Transparency mode</p>



<p>Personalized Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking</p>



<p>H1 chip</p>



<p>Hey&nbsp;Siri</p>



<p>Up to 20 hours of listening time on one charge</p>



<p>Automatic switching</p>



<p>Personalized engraving</p>



<p>Smart Case</p>
</div></div>



<h2 class="has-luminous-vivid-amber-background-color has-text-color has-background" style="color:#144d26"> AirPods&nbsp;Max price is $549</h2>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-much-are-airpods/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
